Ok, wait, listen to this:
There is a moment.
A moment when everything fits.
The light.
The shadows.
The music.
The words.
You're there, in front of the screen,
and for one tiny yet infinite instant,
you feel...
something
Not satisfaction.
Something much better.
A spark of electricity
rising from your fingers
to the back of your head.
The perfect video.
You did it.
It is real.
Here and now.
And in that moment,
you think,
oh God.
This feels better than anything.
Better than a morning cup of coffee.
Better than remembering a password.
It's perfect.
Literally perfect.
And for a nanosecond
you don't need anything
else in the world.
Anything to change.
No complaints.
No doubts.
No...
could it be better?
Because it's already the best.
And your body knows it
You feel it in your chest,
in your temples,
pulsing with every cut of the video
that seems made
just
for
you
But of course,
the magic never lasts.
Because just when you're at the peak
just when you think
you've found the best thing you'll ever see
that
little
shadow
appears
in
your
mind
A whisper:
what if?
Two words that change everything
What if there's something beyond this?
Something even better?
It's not that there's anything wrong,
of course not, but
you know...
Something that doesn't just make you feel
but completely wrecks you.
Your finger,
frozen just a second ago,
comes to life
Scroll.
Every movement
is like turning
a key in a lock
whose destination
you don't know,
but you know
you have to open it.
Because:
what if the next video
is the one?
Not this one.
Not the next
The next one.
It's like scrolling
is an endless spell,
because of course,
you know there are
good things.
Of course
there are.
But you're not here
for good things
Because good things
are easy.
Good things are everywhere.
Good things are forgettable.
You're here looking
for what you might call,
if you were brave enough
to put it into words
PERFECTION.
Wait,
you've found it again,
haven't you?
How long did that
"moment when everything clicks"
last this time?
10 seconds?
09 seconds?
08 seconds?
07 seconds?
06 seconds?
05 seconds?
04 seconds?
03 seconds?
02 seconds?
01 second?
Less?
Don't fool yourself.
You know
as well as I do
that spark can't last.
This is
where
things
get
complicated
That next
video.
The
one
after
the
next
after
the
next
Might be the one
You're looking for
or not
But can you stop?
Stop searching?
It's like
flipping
a coin
over
and
hoping
one
day
it
lands
on
it's
edge
And you know what?
Sometimes,
it does.
And that's when
you get it:
it is not about
the perfect video
it is about the search
It's simple
It's yours.
No one else
understand it
the way you do.
Because even though
millions of people
are doing
the same thing
scrollllling
just
like
you
each
one
follows
their
own
algorithm.
A kind of
modern miracle
though no one
wants to
admit it
because, of course,
who
wants
to
admit
they
spend
bloody
hours
scrolling
on
their
phone
[commercial break]
but here you are.
and it's perfect.
Some might call it
a waste of time,
that you could be doing
something more..
productive.
but so what?
The obsession with productivity is,
at it's core,
a sophisticated trap.
We've been sold
the idea that
every minute
must be invested
in something:
"useful"
something that moves forward.
As if life were
a puzzle with
a clear final picture.
This need to be
constantly efficient
turns even leisure
into a task;
something that
must be
optimized,
structured.
But what if it's not?
What if it's simply
about filling the spaces
with things that make us
feel something,
regardless of
their tangible value
Sometimes,
life is nothing more than
moments,
one after another.
Some of those
are as simple as
scrolling up.
Letting the screen
decide wha'ts next
In search of the perfect video
because my friend
how good it feels to be
that close.,